Defending Santa is a comedy, family, tv movie film directed by Brian Skiba.
Kris Kringle, aka Santa Claus, goes on trial for
mental competency in Small Town U.S.A.
Sheriff Scott Hanson, played by Dean Cain.
Sarah Walker, played by Jud Tylor.
Judge Willis, played by John Savage.
Robert Nielson, played by Gary Hudson.
William, played by Eric Scott Woods.
Kris Kringle, played by Bill Lewis.
Rush is a 2013 biographical sports film directed by
Ron Howard and written by Peter Morgan.
It is centred on the rivalry between two Formula One drivers, James
Hunt and Niki Lauda, during the 1976 Formula One season.
The film stars Chris Hemsworth as Hunt and Daniel Brühl as Lauda.
The film premiered in London on 2 September 2013 and was shown at the 2013 Toronto
International Film Festival before its United Kingdom release on 13 September 2013.
The film received positive reviews from critics for Hemsworth and Brühl's performances,
Howard's direction, the racing sequences, and Hans Zimmer's musical score.
The tone is lighthearted.